# Francesca Paris

francescaparis90@gmail.com | London | 07878491071

#### PROFILE \_

Creative professional with experience in 3D art, web design and digital marketing, working both independently and within a team. Methodical and well organised, enjoys solving problems and learning new skills. Good IT literacy and quick learner.

### SKILLS =

- Game art: 3D modelling, texturing, creation of materials and scenes inside game engines
- Web design: WYSIWYG software, CMS (Joomla, Drupal, Wordpress), FTP software.
- **Graphic Design:** Photo-editing skills (Photoshop), vector graphics (Illustrator).
- Video-editing: Da Vinci Resolve, Handbrake
- **Marketing:** Google AdWords, Google Analytics, social media (Facebook, Twitter, Tumblr, Pinterest, Instagram and YouTube)
- Project Management: Trello, Asana
- Office and communication tools: Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, Microsoft Word, Google Docs, EverNote, Dropbox, Slack and Discord
- Languages: Fluent in written and spoken English. Italian native speaker

#### EXPERIENCE

#### 3D ARTIST | FUTURIUM

2018 - 2020

Bangor, UK

- Creating 3D models: floorplans, houses, environments using our asset library and following the architect specification sheets. Occasionally I also have to create 3D assets for the assets library.
- Creating the final 3D environment using Unity and the company's tools.
- Adapting textures whenever necessary using Adobe Photoshop.
- Working within a team, collaborating on projects with tight deadlines

# DIGITAL AND CONTENT MARKETING EXECUTIVE CIVIL SERVICE | GRUPPO TRENTINO DI VOLONTARIATO

2017 - 2018

Trento, Italy

- Writing articles and creating web pages using Joomla and Adobe Spark Page
- Social media content creation and moderation: Instagram and Facebook
- Data analysis and reporting (Google Analytics, Google Business, Facebook Insight and Instagram Insights)
- Developing a content calendar and managing content releases on the different digital channels (website, social media, newsletter)
- Managing the contacts database (Microsoft Excel / Open Office Calc)
- Creating Newsletters
- Managing marketing campaigns (Google Adwords)

## GAME ARTIST | FREELANCING

2016 - 2018

I worked with 3 start ups on the following game projects: Dominatio AR, Mysteries of Genesis and a tower defence game. My tasks included:

- Creating 3D models and textures
- Checking the models inside a game engine and create materials.

# GAME ARTIST AND GAME DESIGNER INTERNSHIP | COREHAB

Trento, Italy

My tasks included game design aspects, such as generating new game ideas and game mechanics. I was also responsible of creating 2D concept art, 3D modelling and texturing.

### **EDUCATION**

FEB - APR 2017

ONLINE COURSE: UE4 MODULAR ENVIRONMENTS
COMPUTER GRAPHICS MASTER ACADEMY

OCT - DEC 2016

ONLINE COURSE: INTRO TO ENVIRONMENT ART
COMPUTER GRAPHICS MASTER ACADEMY

2011 - 2014

BA GAMES DESIGN
UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL LANCASHIRE (UK)

2:1 Honours Degree